zoombli.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy Policy

Zoombli takes your privacy as seriously as you do. Respecting your privacy is our lifeblood because without customers like you we have no business. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use personal information such as your name and email address. We hope that this will help you to make informed decisions when visiting our web sites, buying from us, or otherwise using our services.

Zoombli voluntarily adheres to the Safe Harbor Agreement concerning the transfer of personal data from the European Union to the United States. Accordingly, we follow the Safe Harbor Principles published by the U.S. Department of Commerce ("Principles") with respect to all such data. The Principles can be found at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/SHPRINCIPLESFINAL.htm>. If there is any conflict between this Privacy Policy ("Policy") and the Principles, the Principles will govern. 

##### What This Privacy Policy Covers and Applies To

This Privacy Policy covers how Zoombli treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name or email address. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services, and websites offered by Zoombli. In this Privacy Policy, references to "we", "our" and "us" refer to Zoombli while "you" and "your" refer to you, the customer or user. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Zoombli does not own or control or to people that Zoombli does not employ or manage.

##### Information We Collect

We collect personal information when you subscribe to one of our newsletters, download a trial version of a product being promoted by us, or purchase a product or service from us. The type of information we collect may vary based upon the way we interact with you. For example, if you sign up for a newsletter we may only collect your name and email address. However, if you make a purchase from us then we may also collect your credit card number and physical address in order to complete the purchase and deliver any physical products. We may combine information that we have about you with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

Zoombli automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Zoombli cookie information, and pages you request. This is done as part of regular internet communication between a browser and a web site.

##### How We Use Collected Information

Zoombli uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

##### CONSENT

BY USING OUR SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PRIVACY POLICY. BECAUSE WE OPERATE GLOBALLY, WE MAKE INFORMATION WE GATHER AVAILABLE TO OUR WORLDWIDE BUSINESS UNITS. FOR THOSE OF YOU VISITING US FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, CANADA, OR OTHER JURISDICTIONS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES, PLEASE NOTE THAT THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU ENTER WILL BE TRANSFERRED OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN UNION OR YOUR HOME COUNTRY FOR USE BY US AND OUR AFFILIATES FOR ONE OR MORE OF THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY. YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED AND STORED IN THE UNITED STATES, AND AS A RESULT, GOVERNMENTS, COURTS, OR LAW ENFORCEMENT OR REGULATORY AGENCIES MAY BE ABLE TO OBTAIN DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION THROUGH LAWS APPLICABLE IN THE UNITED STATES. BY USING OUR SITE AND PROVIDING US WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU CONSENT TO THIS TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

##### Children

This site is not aimed to attract children and its objective is not to collect personal information from children. Anyone under the age of 18 should not use this site unless supervised by an adult. Zoombli’s goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to collection and use of information from children, including the Children’s On-line Privacy Protection Act of the United States.

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Zoombli does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Zoombli under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Zoombli communicate with you (for example, email service providers). These companies, however, do not have any independent right to use or share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Zoombli’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Zoombli is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Zoombli will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * Zoombli may display targeted offers based on personal information. Advertisers may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted offers meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
  * Zoombli does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or complete a targeted offer. By interacting with or viewing an offer, however, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

##### Cookies

Zoombli may set and access Zoombli cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Zoombli's cookies. Zoombli uses web beacons to access Zoombli cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Zoombli products and services.

##### General

You can edit your personal information stored by us at any time by utilizing web services, if available, or by contacting us via one of the methods listed at the end of this policy.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to Zoombli, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part an established business relationship, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Zoombli is a trade name for certain web stores and services offered by support.com, Inc. or its subsidiary, SDC Software, Inc. As used in this agreement, support.com, Inc., its divisions, trade names, subsidiaries, and affiliated companies and entities are collectively referred to as "Zoombli" or "support.com." We reserve the right to use information about you in accordance with this policy for all support.com subsidiaries and divisions and under all support.com trade names. 

##### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

##### Contact Us

Zoombli may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address in our file for you or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@zoombli.com](mailto:support@zoombli.com) or write to us at Privacy Concerns, c/o Zoombli, 23316 NE Redmond-Fall City Road, #667, Redmond, WA 98053.

##### Last Updated December 21st, 2009
